[Professional subtitles are being translated. Will be updated soon]
【专业字幕正在翻译中。很快就会更新]
lecturer
讲师
Any other questions today?
今天还有其他问题吗？
nothing
没有任何东西
Then I'll go do other work first.
那我先去干别的工作了。
let's go.
我们走吧。
able
能
I'll start by looking at the sample library.
我先看一下示例库。
Yes, this way.
是的，这边走。
Why?
为什么？
that woman
那个女人
This person is Dr. Pianchi.
这个人就是皮安奇博士。
B13 project leader
B13项目负责人
Passed by just now
刚才路过
Who is that woman?
那个女人是谁？
Dr. Pianchi's Assistant
皮安奇博士的助手
My name is Yu Xiaoyue.
我叫于小月。
This path is the sample library.
这条路就是示例库。
every time i collect and save
每次我收集并保存
will be saved on this computer.
将保存在此计算机上。
Stone, come and take a look.
石头，过来看看。
Example of B13
B13的例子
Stored in this liquid nitrogen tank.
储存在这个液氮罐中。
And there are
而且还有
CCTV cameras 24 hours a day
闭路电视摄像机全天 24 小时
So this situation is impossible to happen.
所以这种情况是不可能发生的。
Missing examples
缺少示例
B13
B13
Today is five minutes after midnight.
今天是午夜过后五分钟。
I went into the warehouse once.
我进过一次仓库。
B13 The last result came out today.
B13 今天最后一次结果出来了。
ten minutes ago
十分钟前
Where can I view CCTV cameras?
我在哪里可以查看闭路电视摄像机？
You can look at it this way.
你可以这样看。
Please come this way.
请这边来。
look.
看。
Examples like this
像这样的例子
In the laboratory
在实验室
After the division is completed
分割完成后
Gradually sent to sample warehouse
逐步送往样品仓库
Let's freeze it.
让我们冻结吧。
Look at this bottle of liquid nitrogen.
你看这瓶液氮。
its temperature
它的温度
minus 160 degrees
负160度
to 170 degrees
至 170 度
for long term preservation
为了长期保存
Is there CCTV in the lab?
实验室有闭路电视吗？
have.
有。
Can you see this?
你能看到这里吗？
can be seen
可以看到
But the experimental process
但实验过程
involves high confidentiality
涉及高度保密
Must be handed over to the president of the company
必须交给公司总裁
Approval is correct.
批准是正确的。
if you want to see
如果你想看
I can refer the matter to you immediately.
我可以立即将此事提交给您。
Then I'll trouble you.
那我就麻烦你了。
It doesn't matter
没关系
stop
停止
Stand back a little.
往后退一点。
enlarge it
放大它
You look at her hands.
你看着她的手。
Except for straws
除了吸管
It seems like there is something else.
好像还有别的东西。
It looks like a needle.
它看起来像一根针管。
next place
下一个地方
stop
停止
Look at that posture.
你看看那个姿势。
Just like putting it in a bag.
就像把它放进袋子里一样。
put something on
穿上一些东西
Yes
是的
this woman
这个女人
Hurry and find out where she is.
赶紧找出她在哪里。
You can find it here.
你可以在这里找到它。
Can CCTV cameras be used in public areas?
公共区域可以使用闭路电视摄像机吗？
Can't see it here
这里看不到
I brought it to you
我给你们带来了
Go to the public CCTV room.
前往公共闭路电视室。
That's right, when leaving the lobby.
没错，离开大厅的时候。
She had to pass a security check.
她必须通过安全检查。
Da Liu, you went to the security check.
大刘，你去安检了。
goodbye
再见
Mainly checked her bag.
主要是检查了她的包。
And things to take with you.
还有随身携带的东西。
Yes
是的
Shitou went to the CCTV room.
石头去了闭路电视室。
able
能
follow me.
跟我来。
did you find it?
你找到了吗？
She comes out of the lab.
她从实验室出来。
Go to the bathroom first.
先去趟卫生间。
Then he went to the locker room.
然后就去了更衣室。
daliu daliu
大六大六
Where did the target go?
目标去哪儿了？
West side of the institute
研究院西侧
Big Liu
大刘
What is Yu Xiaoyue doing?
余小月这是在做什么？
Yu Xiaoyue sat down and packed her things.
余小月坐下来，收拾起了自己的东西。
She threw the sample out the window.
她把样品从窗户扔了出去。
This is to avoid security checks.
这是为了避免安全检查。
What should I do now?
我现在应该怎么做？
Haven't caught it yet.
还没抓住它。
Still not sure
仍不确定
Is she a professor?
她是教授吗？
Look who she's dealing with.
看看她在和谁打交道。
Now ready to leave the academy.
现在准备离开学院。
do you understand?
你懂了吗？
Keep an eye on her.
留意她。
admit
承认
Hello
你好
I'm going out.
我出去了。
Okay, I see you now.
好的，我现在看到你了。
The goal of online booking
网上预约的目标
Vehicle registration DC0513
车辆登记 DC0513
boss
老板
Hello, a bag of ice.
你好，一袋冰。
Hello, two yuan, five yuan.
你好，两元，五元。
you do not say.
你不说。
Equipment for this game
本游戏的装备
You can do it very seriously.
你可以非常认真地去做。
Examples of some organisms
一些生物的例子
during shipping
运输过程中
The temperature must be kept very low.
温度必须保持很低。
Do you still know about biology?
你还了解生物吗？
I know a little bit.
我知道一点。
Now the more I count the days, the more I believe
现在我越数着日子就越相信
What we hold is
我们所持有的是
Examples of real creatures
真实生物的例子
It can be used here, Huang Dayang.
这里可以用，黄大阳。
You get so deeply invested in this character.
你对这个角色的投入非常深。
this game
这个游戏
The further back I went, the more excited I became.
越往后走，我就越兴奋。
Need I say more?
我还需要说吗？
By the way, where is the pick-up location?
对了，上车地点在哪里？
Go to Waterfront Park
前往海滨公园
suspect's destination
嫌疑人的目的地
This is a seaside park.
这是海滨公园。
The technical department is ready.
技术部已做好准备。
She might be able to get the job done there.
她也许能够在那里完成工作。
It has passed.
已经过去了。
Do you know the basics?
你知道基本情况吗？
Yu Xiaoyue
于小月
Gimhae University College of Biomedicine
金海大学生物医学学院
Yanshan students
燕山学生
Dr. Byun, laboratory leader
Byun博士，实验室负责人
become her advisor
成为她的顾问
Yu Xiaoyue, at the beginning of this year
于小月，今年年初
Go to the laboratory to practice
去实验室实践
also
此外
She also has another side job.
她还有另一份副业。
a little famous person
一个小有名气的人
relatively reputable
小有名气
Because the face is not bad
因为脸不差
usually do
通常做
Simple popular science video
简单的科普视频
Online fan club
在线粉丝俱乐部
Already almost half a million
已经快五十万了
What is your current occupation?
你现在的职业是什么？
You can also become an internet idol.
你也可以成为网络偶像。
Of course, it’s okay to eat loudly.
当然，大声吃饭还是可以的。
The pony followed her.
小马跟着她。
Another one, another one, go, go.
另一个，另一个，走，走。
Someone went in.
有人进去了。
stop stop stop
停止停止停止
What’s wrong with you?
你怎么了？
How did he get here?
他是怎么到这里来的？
do you know?
你知道吗？
my brother
我的弟弟
is it here?
是这里吗？
here
这里
let's go.
我们走吧。
Not you, what are you doing?
不是你，你在做什么？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Can't you act in a drama?
你就不能演话剧吗？
In the world of spies
在间谍的世界里
Must always have access to this role
必须始终有权访问该角色
access role
访问角色
don't don't don't don't
别别别别
Absolutely not.
绝对不是。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
That is,
那是，
Put it on me first
先给我戴上吧
Why
为什么
Are you still afraid that I will run away?
你还怕我逃跑吗？
who knows?
谁知道？
in spy games
在间谍游戏中
I'm famous too
我也出名了
I'll go investigate.
我去调查一下。
You have a bad reputation.
你的名声很糟糕。
These are all rumors.
这都是谣言。
Clearly jealous
明显嫉妒了
I only believe in my own decisions.
我只相信我自己的决定。
Keep 4 degrees
保持4度
sorry.
对不起。
This thermos cup
这个保温杯
It's still in my bag.
它还在我的包里。
By the way, give me a drink.
对了，给我一杯。
Assume I know the game.
假设我知道这个游戏。
Why design a companion?
为什么要设计伴侣？
You already knew that, right?
你已经知道了，对吧？
This is to warn you.
这是为了警告你。
Don't always be complacent.
不要总是自满。
Who knows what your partner will be?
谁知道你的伴侣会是什么？
get away
逃离
When did you start running away?
你从什么时候开始逃走的？
In the world of spies
在间谍的世界里
can't trust anyone
不能相信任何人
Even the people around you
甚至你身边的人
You must always be careful.
你必须时刻小心。
The next station is
下站是
Bangkok
曼谷
suppose i know
假设我知道
Task prompt time
任务提示时间
Why
为什么
Please bring your bag and passport with you.
请随身携带您的包和护照。
It looks like it was designed a long time ago.
看起来好像是很久以前设计的。
let's go.
我们走吧。
We went to the airport.
我们去了机场。
this game
这个游戏
something
有些东西
You don't have to worry this time, right?
这次你不用担心了，对吧？
Now the two of us are inseparable.
现在我们两个已经形影不离了。
let's go.
我们走吧。
Samples have been collected.
样品已采集。
Targeting
目标锁定
One man and one woman
一男一女
A 28-year-old man was sitting in the car.
车内坐着一名28岁的男子。
Put on a white coat
穿上白大褂
Black double bag
黑色双包
Height approx. 180 cm
高度约180厘米
His name is Huang Zicheng, I know.
名字叫黄子成，我知道。
I don't know the woman's identity.
我不知道该女子的身份。
It's up to me to follow up on the rest.
剩下的就由我来跟进了。
I'd like some advice.
我想要一些建议。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I've thought about it.
我已经考虑过了。
is that so?
是这样吗？
Must be kept at 4 degrees.
必须保持在4度。
Otherwise, place in a heatproof cup first.
否则，先放入耐热杯。
Don't do it because of this
别因为这个
mission failed.
任务失败。
Then you get me a thermos cup.
然后你给我拿一个保温杯。
Have you read and understood what it is?
您读过并理解它是什么吗？
Take a look too.
你也看看。
Quality blurred, layered
质量模糊、分层
Must remain below center
必须保持在中心下方
From the knowledge I gathered
从我收集的知识来看
This could be some kind of experimental medicine.
这可能是某种实验医学。
And you do know this.
你也确实知道这一点。
affim
肯定
Someone in our family does this.
我们家有人做这件事。
seen it myself
亲眼所见
but
但
Even if this is a real example
即使这是一个真实的例子
this is normal.
这是正常的。
It can be seen that the task positioning is very strict.
可见任务定位十分严格。
that's right.
这是正确的。
But why am I still
但为什么我还是
a little excited
有点兴奋
you are like this
你是这样的
Are you still playing offline missions?
还在玩离线任务吗？
I'm careful, aren't I?
我很小心，不是吗？
I get it, I totally get it.
我明白了，我彻底明白了。
That's your type
你就是这样的类型
Dare to speak and act in the game
游戏中敢说、敢做
When it comes to your life, you're already wandering.
当谈到你的生活时，你已经在徘徊了。
who who who
谁谁谁
Who, who, I understand.
谁，谁，我明白了。
I get it, I totally get it.
我明白了，我完全明白了。
There are no letters in my dictionary\215;
在我的字典里没有字母\215；
I see
我明白
So I'm not worried about you being scared.
所以我不担心你害怕。
Please hurry up.
请快点。
Yaoyao, woman
瑶瑶，女人
25 years old, from Jinhai
25岁，金海人
Have study abroad background
有留学背景
At the end of last year, I returned to China.
去年年底，我回国了。
It happened many times during this period.
这期间出现过很多次。
Immigration records
出入境记录
Set aside two goals.
预留两个目标。
It's half past six tonight.
今晚六点半了。
Flight tickets to Bangkok
飞往 曼谷 的机票
Huang Zichengnan
黄子成 男
28 years old, from Jinhai
28岁，金海人
Kimhae University
金海大学
Data Engineering Academy Online
数据工程学院在线
Graduate with a bachelor's degree
毕业并获得学士学位
There is currently no job agency.
目前尚无工作机构。
best in game
游戏中最好的
When I was in college, I used to put together a team.
当我在大学的时候，我曾经组建过一个团队。
Participate in the competition
参加比赛
international gaming competition
国际游戏比赛
and gain military rank
并获得军衔
many years ago
多年前
There are multiple entries and exits recorded.
有多次进出记录。
Gao Tianyang's younger brother.
高天阳的弟弟。
Director Qin
秦主任
should i avoid
我应该避免
Emergency situations
紧急情况
You continue this mission.
你继续这个使命。
You should know
你应该知道
in the face of national interests
在国家利益面前
Keep your personal feelings to yourself.
保持好你的个人感情。
If Huang Zicheng goes abroad
如果黄子成出国
Will you be quarantined?
你会被隔离吗？
I will send
我会发
agency inspector
机构检查人员
go to airport
去机场
When you are sure the sample is authentic
当您确定样品是真实的时
Quarantine immediately
立即隔离
I see.
我明白。
Please check it for me.
请帮我检查一下。
Is this an example of B13?
这是 B13 的例子吗？
Ok, no problem.
好的，没问题。
I gotta go
我要走了
Are you OK
你好吗
Ordinary honey
普通蜂蜜
You're already in trouble.
你已经有麻烦了。
It doesn't matter
没关系
Fortunately the sample is fake.
还好样品是假的。
if it is like this
如果是这样的话
We have to hurry up.
我们得快点。
real example
真实的例子
has changed
已经变了
I would like to know
我想知道
two of them are
其中两个是
Gamers who complete special tasks
完成特殊任务的游戏玩家
Huang Zicheng
黄子成
really like playing games
真的很喜欢玩游戏
if he is
如果他是
Gamers who were actually chosen by spies
真正被间谍选中的游戏玩家
If the spies still plan to use him
如果间谍还打算利用他
He is safe now.
他现在安全了。
don’t worry.
别担心。
Our top priority now
现在我们的当务之急
That is, take missing samples.
即，取缺失的样本。
Yu Xiaoyue left the institute.
于小月离开了研究所。
always in our sight
始终在我们的视线里
If anyone wants to change the sample
如果有人想改变样品
Probably
很有可能
Before Xiao Yue left the institute
肖月离开研究所前
I sent someone to check.
我派人去查了。
I'm thinking
我在想
This is Yu Xiaoyue
这个于小月
Is she a professor?
她是教授吗？
Hello
你好
Gaoke
高克
I checked the security cameras.
我检查了安全摄像头。
Yu Xiaoyue confirmed
于晓月证实
After leaving the sample
离开样品后
A cleaning crew has arrived at the scene.
一名清洁人员已赶到现场。
Cleaning staff
清洁人员
Have you checked the shift schedule?
你查过轮班表吗？
Verified
已验证
Let your real estate company schedule a cleaning today.
今天就让您的房地产公司安排清洁工作。
There are no men.
没有男人。
Where did he leave?
他离开哪里了？
Come out the back door.
从后门出来。
There are no security cameras outside.
外面没有安全摄像头。
I have contacted the technical department.
我已经联系了技术部门。
Ask them to check the CCTV cameras on the streets.
让他们检查街上的闭路电视摄像机。
Yes
是的
Thanks
谢谢
Tian Yang, here I come.
田阳，我来了。
OK
好的
He walked straight across the road.
他笔直地穿过马路。
admit
承认
Continue walking straight.
继续笔直行走。
There is a cold chain truck parked on the roadside.
路边停着一辆冷链车。
Just like you're taking a photo.
就像你在拍照一样。
The subject walks past a refrigerated truck.
目标走过一辆冷藏车。
From the perspective of CCTV
从央视这个角度来看
I will never see him again.
我再也见不到他了。
After passing the refrigerated truck
经过冷藏车后
The target appears from behind the car again.
目标再次从车后出现。
impossible
不可能的
We walk at a normal pace.
我们以正常的速度行走。
He has no choice
他没有办法
This is too slow.
这太慢了。
Unless you stop halfway.
除非你中途停下来。
according to his speed
根据他的速度
Only a few seconds slower than us.
只比我们慢了几秒钟。
It may be too late.
可能来不及了。
But he has enough time.
但他有足够的时间。
Go around the back of the car and lower the trailer.
绕过汽车后部并将拖车放下。
It may well have been delivered.
它很可能已经交付了。
But the CCTV cameras here
但这里的闭路电视摄像机
It's not okay to take pictures like this
这样拍照就不行了
Find a way to check it out.
想办法检查一下。
CCTV camera of normal shop next door
隔壁正常商店的闭路电视摄像机
And this cool truck.
还有这辆很酷的卡车。
Must be fast
一定要快
admit
承认
He continued speaking straightly.
他继续笔直地说道。
he went in
他进去了
The underground shopping mall next door
隔壁地下商场
The goal is lost here.
这里就失去了目标。
No security cameras?
没有安全摄像头吗？
He was not visible on CCTV cameras.
闭路电视摄像机看不到他。
It seems he has been planning this for a long time.
看来他已经计划了很久了。
This road has been missing for a long time.
这条路已经消失很长时间了。
The clue disappeared.
线索消失了。
All we can do is wait.
我们能做的就是等待。
Results from the CCTV cameras there.
那里的闭路电视摄像机的结果。
Yu Xiaoyue?
于小月？
close to you
接近你的
Japanese restaurant called "The Fisherman"
名为“渔夫”的日本餐厅
She said, Yu Xiaoyue, do you know?
她说于小月你知道吗？
The sample she stole had been replaced.
她偷来的样本已经被替换了。
have no idea
不知道
she may
她可能
This is one of the professor's works.
这是教授的作品之一。
Then we have to be more careful.
那我们就得更加小心了。
go to eat
去吃饭
Is it Japanese food?
是日本菜吗？
I lift it myself
我自己举
for work
为了工作
welcome
欢迎
Two people?
两个人？
Yes
是的
This way
这边走
staff
员工
Thanks
谢谢
Hold on
稍等
I
我
welcome
欢迎
What do you two want to eat?
你们两个想吃什么？
Our tuna is a label.
我们的金枪鱼是一个标签。
You come.
你来。
We ate very easily.
我们吃得很轻松。
Yes
是的
Order the tuna salad.
点一份金枪鱼沙拉。
Please give me some beef rice.
请给我一些牛肉饭。
Hello
你好
I got another order of fried chicken.
我又拿了一份炸鸡。
and Japanese cold noodles
和日式冷面
Is it enough?
够了吗？
enough
足够的
OK
好的
Wait a moment, it's almost done.
稍等一下，快完成了。
Thanks
谢谢
I'll go to the bathroom first.
我先去趟洗手间。
Yes
是的
The employee asked for another drink.
员工又要一杯饮料。
Do you think those two friends of yours
你认为你的那两个朋友
Are you OK?
你好吗？
School sweethearts become colleagues
学校恋人成为同事
Men care deeply about women.
男人对女人非常关心。
Too much attention is never a good thing.
太多的关注从来都不是一件好事。
Why?
为什么？
Thanks
谢谢
Are you satisfied?
你满意吗？
Not bad at all
一点也不差
If you like it, fine, enjoy it.
如果你喜欢的话，那就好，吃得香香的。
If you need anything please feel free to give me a call.
如果您需要什么，请随时给我打电话。
This boss
这位老板
Serve us personally.
亲自为我们服务。
Customers are very busy today.
今天顾客很忙。
Then I wish you a prosperous business.
那么祝您生意兴隆。
Thanks
谢谢
It's already difficult.
已经很难了。
You also follow your friends.
你也关注你的朋友。
Don't just look at the boss.
不要只看老板。
Boss Nian is really kind-hearted.
年老板真是心地善良。
Can I ask for your attention?
可以请您注意一下吗？
It usually unfolds like this.
通常都是这样展开的。
So at work
所以在工作中
I will never miss it.
我永远不会错过它。
I know what's going on in your mind.
我知道你心里在想什么。
Don't let me touch your little tail.
别让我碰你的小尾巴。
Am I really that callous?
我真的有那么冷酷无情吗？
You are not mentally ill.
你没有精神病。
That's your pride.
那是你的骄傲。
but now
但现在
It has developed a lot.
已经发展很多了。
You probably won't.
你可能不会。
Do you still want revenge?
你还想报仇吗？
How could I be so narrow-minded?
我怎么可以这么狭隘呢？
actually
实际上
work with you
和你一起工作
That's very good.
那挺好的。
life cannot
生活不能
It's a bit inconsistent
有点不太相符啊
Your friend has been found.
你的朋友已经找到了。
You hurry up and eat.
你赶紧吃饭吧。
So you ordered everything?
所以你订购了所有东西？
Don't waste it.
不要浪费它。
I'll pay
我去付钱
Do you still find traces of the car?
你还发现汽车的痕迹吗？
I gotta go
我要走了
Send me the car registration certificate.
把汽车登记证发给我。
It's him
是他
This is it.
就是这个。
Do you know this person?
你认识这个人吗？
I definitely know it’s Boss Han.
我肯定知道，是韩老板。
He is the boss of the Red Snapper King.
他是红鲷鱼王的老大。
boss
老板
Yes
是的
His family is the Tuna family.
他的家族是金枪鱼家族。
Honourable
光荣的
It is located on the road north of the market.
它位于市场北边的路上。
It's not far away, we are there.
距离不远，我们就在那里。
So the warehouse belongs to him?
那么仓库是他家的？
No, this is a rental.
不，这是出租。
Trucks and warehouses
货车和仓库
They are all home rental services.
它们都是房屋租赁服务。
Provide rental services
提供租赁服务
The owner delivers the goods himself.
业主亲自送货。
The boss is really attentive.
老板真的很用心。
Samples must be kept at low temperatures.
样品必须保存在低温下。
Items may be hidden.
项目可能被隐藏。
Put it in the box of merchandise he sent back to the warehouse.
放在他寄回仓库的商品箱里。
Difficulty entering the position
进仓困难
I have a method.
我有一个方法。
Do not cut grass to scare snakes.
不要割开草丛来惊吓蛇。
affim
肯定
Already have this
已经有这个了
boss
老板
Hello you both.
你们俩好。
please disturb me please disturb me
请打扰我 请打扰我
Look at this fish.
你看看这条鱼。
Do you two want anything?
你们两个想要什么吗？
Both of us
我们俩
from zhouzhouzhou
来自周洲周
I want to open a fresh food supermarket.
我想开一家生鲜超市。
Open your own fresh food supermarket
开设自己的生鲜超市
I spent a whole day shopping here today.
今天我在这里逛了一整天。
I want to find a reliable supplier.
我想找到一个可靠的供应商。
tuna suppliers
金枪鱼供应商
Come and have a look.
过来看看吧。
Want to start your own small business
想创办自己的小企业
Yes Yes
是的是的
So if you are looking for tuna
所以如果你正在寻找金枪鱼
You've come to the right place.
您来对地方了。
I
我
well educated
受过良好教育
Really?
真的吗？
look.
你看。
This is awesome.
这个太棒了。
Are you all fishermen?
你们都是渔民吗？
not all
不是全部
There are fishing enthusiasts in every country.
每个国家都有钓鱼爱好者。
They are all very noble.
他们都非常高贵。
fishing technician
钓鱼技术员
Then you are still a person who likes fishing.
那你还是一个喜欢钓鱼的人。
It can't be called a hobby.
不能说是爱好。
I can say that I am fishing in the sea.
我可以说是在海里钓鱼。
crazy people
疯狂的人
you can see.
你可以看到。
And Jinhai has
而金海则有
How about a fishing club?
钓鱼俱乐部怎么样？
there must be
肯定有
I am a club member
我是俱乐部会员
Are you interested?
你们有兴趣吗？
Welcome all friends to join us.
欢迎各位朋友的加入。
That's good.
那就好了。
I haven't introduced myself yet.
我还没自我介绍呢。
My name is Han Jie.
我的名字是韩杰。
The owner of this store
这家店的老板
Hello, Tao Kaihan.
你好，陶凯汉。
Hello
你好
our fish
我们的鱼
It's all here, right?
一切都在这里，对吗？
Impossible, can't let go
不可能，放不下
We have a dedicated cold room behind us.
我们身后有一个专用的冷藏室。
Because it must have a specific temperature.
因为它必须有一个特定的温度。
save these tuna
保存这些金枪鱼
So is it convenient for you?
那么你方便吗？
Can we go and have a look?
可以让我们去看看吗？
Now?
现在？
Isn't it very convenient?
是不是很方便？
This is not inconvenient.
这并不不方便。
But not for too long.
但时间不能太长。
because of this fish
因为这条鱼
I see.
我明白。
Yes Yes.
是的是的。
So I'm interrupting you.
所以我打扰你了。
Yes, let's go.
是的，走吧。
Come on, follow me.
来吧，跟我来。
OK, let’s go.
好，出发。
The temperature inside is quite low.
里面的温度相当低。
Come on.
来来。
It's a bit cold inside.
里面有点冷。
lying on the floor
躺在地板上
It is imported from various sources.
它是从各个来源进口的。
blue stingray gold spear
蓝色黄貂鱼金矛
Most are Australian snails.
大多数是澳大利亚蜗牛。
And blue stingrays.
还有蓝色黄貂鱼。
Of course there is.
当然有。
golden marlin
黄金枪鱼
Stingray Golden Spear Price
黄貂鱼金矛价格
will be quite high
会相当高
There are many choices in the domestic market.
国内市场有很多选择。
It mainly depends on your needs.
主要还是看你的需求。
It's the same with humans.
人类也是一样的。
Rely on one's own strength
靠自己的力量
Take the Golden Spear from the Blue Stingray.
拿走蓝黄貂鱼的金矛。
Eat until it's dangerous.
吃到危险为止。
no way.
没办法。
There is demand in this market.
这个市场有需求。
how?
如何？
In the eyes of most customers
在大多数顾客眼中
This golden gun, this blue gun.
这金枪，这蓝枪。
Fresh
新鲜
it reflects
它反映了
High level Japanese food
高水平的日本料理
this is correct.
这是对的。
Do we have fresh fish?
我们有新鲜的鱼吗？
Yes, this is the way to go.
是的，这条路就到了。
then we
然后我们
will be sent to
将发送至
including degree of freshness
包括保鲜程度
Can I guarantee this?
我能保证这一点吗？
This is something you can count on.
这是您可以信赖的。
We are all degrees zero to four.
我们都是零到四度。
Keep ice fresh
保持冰块新鲜
After the product arrives
产品到达后
Will find an expert immediately
会立即找专家
Cold chain logistics delivery is everywhere.
冷链物流送货无处不在。
If you are in Zhuzhou
如果你们在株洲
You will receive fish that morning.
那天早上你会收到鱼。
In fact, I have many Southeast Asian customers.
事实上，我有很多东南亚客户。
That day they received fish.
那天他们收到了鱼。
your customer
你的客户
It's everywhere indeed.
确实到处都有。
superb
高超
Then this kind of thing bothers you.
那么这种事情就困扰着你了。
The two of us went back and discussed it together.
我们两个回去一起商量了一下。
and contact you later
然后稍后联系您
Ok, no problem
好的没问题
Do you have a business card?
你有名片吗？
Yeah, yeah, look at my brain.
是的，是的，看看我的大脑。
Ma Hengjie
马恒洁
Han Lu
韩律
thanks, thanks.
谢谢谢谢。
sorry.
对不起。
All I have is this electronic business card.
我只有这张电子名片。
able?
能？
No problem, no problem.
没问题，没问题。
you sent it to me
你把它发给我了
So now I'm sending it to you.
所以现在我把它发给你。
Did you get it?
你收到了吗？
Manager Wu
吴经理
Ok, no problem
好的没问题
Come on, I'll take you there first.
来吧，我先送你们去。
Very cold, very cold.
非常冷，非常冷。
go! go! go
去！去！去
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
谢谢你，谢谢你，谢谢你。
Come on, come over here.
来吧，过来这边。
All boxes are the same.
所有盒子都是一样的。
It's hard to tell where to put it.
很难说该把它放在哪里。
You know tuna.
你知道金枪鱼。
we create information
我们制作信息
I have seen quite a lot of the world.
我见过的世界还蛮多的。
this is normal.
这是正常的。
distract you like me
像我一样分散你的注意力
Is it still useful?
还有用吗？
I searched my phone all the way.
我一路搜遍了手机。
Learn it and sell it, right?
学习了然后卖掉吧？
This is the ability to memorize quickly.
这就是快速记忆的能力。
What do you think of Han Jie?
你觉得韩杰怎么样？
He knows the profession very well.
他非常了解这个职业。
like a boss
像一个老板一样
Look at your body and exercise regularly.
看看自己的身材，经常锻炼身体。
Healthy complexion, probably going to the beach often.
健康肤色，可能经常去海边。
I like sea fishing.
我喜欢海钓。
or surfing
或冲浪运动
I couldn't tell his size at all.
我根本看不出他的身材。
How does this relate to missing samples?
这与样本缺失有什么关系？
there are some things
有一些事情
Now I looked and there was nothing.
现在我看了一下，什么也没有。
I'm not sure what will happen next.
我不确定接下来会发生什么。
Yes, there is a reason for this.
是的，这是有原因的。
What to do next?
接下来该如何处理呢？
He is an example.
他就是一个例子。
This is probably the end.
大概就是结局了。
must pass
必须通过
Cold chain transportation channels
冷链运输渠道
send out
发送出去
fit
合身
It has everything here.
这里什么都有。
Are you ready?
准备好了吗？
Already paying attention to his phone.
已经在关注他的手机了。
Please rest assured that the product will arrive tomorrow.
请放心，产品明天一定会到达。
Your electronic business card has done its job.
您的电子名片已经发挥作用。
I found out you took advantage of my people.
我发现你利用了我的人。
Very smooth.
很光滑。
Wait until tomorrow for him to send the package.
等到明天他寄包裹。
we will
我们将
Sample found
找到了样本
Take a look at Hangyul's reception mode,
看看Hangyul的接收模式，
It may have been seized by spies.
它可能已被间谍夺取。
a transportation line
一条交通线
If we have sampled
如果我们已经取样
The other party did not receive the product.
对方没有收到产品。
Then this line is useless.
那么这条线就没用了。
real
真的
Keep Han Jie.
留着韩杰吧。
Will receive more information
将收到更多信息
But we will give Hangyul
但我们会给Hangyul
Unable to send sample.
无法寄出样品。
They can use fake samples.
他们可以使用假样品。
You can lure us away.
你可以把我们引走。
then we can
那么我们就可以
You can give them something fake.
你可以给他们一些假的东西。
Is there insurance?
有保险吗？
Of course, I can't wear eye drops.
当然，我不能带眼药。
We can't lie to them anymore.
不能再骗他们了。
best way for us
对我们来说最好的方式
people from institute
来自研究所的人
Have a set
有一套
Examples of their previous experiments
他们之前的实验示例
Fake samples can be used as real samples.
假样品可以当真样品使用。
Just like this Korean line
就像这条韩律线
We will be able to follow up.
我们将能够跟进。
or you
或者你
Have you been planning this for a long time?
这个计划你已经酝酿很久了吗？
This person's ideas have always been far-fetched.
这个人的想法一直都是很牵强的。
I never knew that before.
我以前从来不知道。
Understandable
可以理解
Anyway, you
无论如何，你
Not very good at discovering
不太善于发现
the advantages of others
别人的优点
This plan requires permission.
该计划需要许可。
There should still be time
应该还有时间吧
The project still exists.
该项目仍然存在。
Let's continue.
我们继续。
Let's go
走吧
Where?
在哪里？
Didn't say there was
没说有
like a storage box
像一个储物盒
Not here.
这里没有。
Right here, right here, right here
就在这里，就在这里，就在这里
right here
就在这儿
What's this?
这是什么？
Hotel address
酒店地址
key card
钥匙卡
Task cost
任务费用
let's go.
走吧，走吧。
right here
就在这儿
Hello
你好
Hello, we are arranging your accommodation.
您好，我们正在安排您的住宿。
Thanks
谢谢
Thank you, no problem.
谢谢，没问题。
Yes
是的
Why?
为什么？
Do you want a drink?
你要喝一杯吗？
The mission is not over yet.
任务还没有结束。
There are new orders every time.
每次都有新订单。
Get some rest now and don't run around.
赶紧休息吧，别到处乱跑。
Why is it different from what I imagined?
为什么和我想象的不一样？
Not the same
不太一样